A story for anyone with an appetite for love.
Feast of Love is a romance, drama film directed by Robert Benton.
A meditation on love and its various incarnations, set
within a community of friends in Oregon.
It is described as an exploration of the magical, mysterious
and sometimes painful incarnations of love.
Harry Stevenson, played by Morgan Freeman.
Bradley Smith, played by Greg Kinnear.
Diana Croce, played by Radha Mitchell.
David Watson, played by Billy Burke.
Kathryn Smith, played by Selma Blair.
Chloe Barlow, played by Alexa Davalos.
Feast of Love is a 2007 American drama film directed by Robert Benton (his last film before his death in 2025), and starring an ensemble cast that
includes Morgan Freeman, Greg Kinnear, Radha Mitchell, Billy Burke, Selma Blair, Alexa Davalos, Toby Hemingway, and Jane Alexander.
The film, based on the 2000 novel The Feast of Love by Charles Baxter, was
first released on September 28, 2007, in the United States.
The film explores themes of adultery, dancing,
friendship, marriage proposal, fortune teller.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.